somewhereinbangladesh.net 2011-11-20

# Untitled Document

privacy policy

somewhere in net ltd. has created this privacy policy in order to demonstrate our commitment to treat personal information with respect and caution.  the following discloses our information gathering and dissemination practices for the sites: [www.somewherein.net](http://www.somewherein.net/), [www.somewhereindhaka.net](http://www.somewhereindhaka.net/), [www.somewhereinblog.net](http://www.somewhereinblog.net/), [www.somewhereinads.net](http://www.somewhereinads.net/) and [www.aawaj.com](http://www.aawaj.com/). 

you can visit our website somewherein.net without telling us who you are or provide information about yourself.  somewhere in’s… web servers only register the domain name (IP address), browser and session information, not your email address or personal name of visitors.  somewhere in… uses this information to analyse the use of our website and continuously improve its quality, monitor and prevent fraud and abuse, help determining privileges and provide more location and topic relevance in content, persons and advertisements.

somewhere in... collects personal information when you register with us or actively participate in our services.  somewhere in... may collect information about your transactions with us or with our business partners if and when you use any of our web and mobile services.  for situations where somewhere in... needs to communicate with you, somewhere in... may contact you to request personal information or feedback from you.  the somewhere in... sites, products and services use personal information for the following purposes: products and services provision, identification and authentication, services improvement, contact, research, recommendations, billing and anonymous reporting.

personal information resides behind a firewall, with access restricted to authorised somewhere in… personnel only.  somewhere in... does not sell or share this information with our advertisers our advertising companies.  however, somewhere in… privacy policy does not cover how mobile phone companies or internet service providers directing traffic to us deal with information before or after using our services.

somewhere in... tries to give registered customers information customised to their personal information.  for this somewhere in... may use cookies.  cookies are stored on your hard drive with the purpose of letting your be recognised next time you visit our page.  you can set your web browser to notify you when you receive a cookie.  you may also block cookies if you want, even though this will prevent us from identifying you and you may not be able to take full advantage of all offerings.  somewhere in... uses cookies for a number of purposes, including to: a) ask you to re-enter your password after a session time is out for security reasons. b) keeping track of your settings.  c) analyse the size and traffic of all usage.  d) improve our products and services. e) ensure that visitors are not shown the same advertisement and to customize advertising based on browser type and user habit information.  f) display user profile and related service feeds through profile widget.  somewhere in...’s cookies are not shared with our business partners.

somewhere in… web sites and mobile services may contain links to other websites.  somewhere in... is not responsible for the privacy practices or content of such websites.

when you provide personal information through somewhere in... you are sharing your personal information with somewhere in... and its affiliated entities, which use is covered by this policy.  though information is not shared with unrelated third parties, somewhere in... may display for you targeted advertisements based on personal information and usage habits. 

somewhere in... may use or share your personal information where it is necessary to complete a transaction, to operate or improve the somewhere in... products and services, to do something that you have asked us to do, or tell you of products and services that somewhere in... thinks may be of interest. 

if you participate willingly in any of our sponsors’ activities, clearly stating the name of the third party, the information you provide may be shared with the same. 

somewhere in... reserve the right to contact you with certain communication related to our products and services, such as service announcements, administrative messages, newsletters and emails without offering you the opportunity to opt-out of receiving them.

somewhere in... collects user-submitted account information such as name, email address, mobile number and age to identify users and send notifications related to the use of the service.  somewhere in... also collects user-submitted profile information, including additional contact information, location, interests, biographical information and photos.  this additional profile information will assist other users in finding and communicating with you.

somewhere in... will store your user data in a central profile to be used by all somewhere in... sites and will display your “display name” and “nick”, if any, along with your submitted content and on your personal pages.  somewhere in... will display your personal information on your personal sites according to the preferences you set in your account. 

somewhere in... will facilitate searching and finding friends and acquaintances on its sites and allows users to search for other members using your “display name.” 

omewhere in... will also allow users to search for you by your first and last name, email address, location, gender, interests or other person specific data according to the preferences you set in your account.

email addresses and full names are used when a user invites a friend via email to join somewhere in..., when a user requests to add another user to their network and when somewhere in... sends notifications to a user related to their use of somewhere in...’s sites.

when you post a message on a somewhere in... site, you have the ability to post a message that includes personally identifiable information about yourself although generally discouraged by somewhere in...

if you post personal information online that is accessible to the public, you may receive unwanted messages from other parties in return.  if you post personal information of others on any of somewhere in...’s sites, this content may be deleted and your account terminated. 

somewhere in... may share personal information about you under the following circumstances:

somewhere in... may share your personal information to respond to written police requests, court orders, or legal process, to establish or exercise our legal rights or, defend against legal claims and if deemed necessary by us to comply with emergency powers or in such circumstances disclosure is appropriate.

somewhere in... may share your personal information if somewhere in... believes it is necessary in order to investigate, prevent, or take action regarding illegal activities, suspected fraud, situations involving potential threats to the physical safety of any person, violations of our various terms of use, or as otherwise required by law.

should a situation arise where somewhere in... will sell all or parts of our business, such transactions, personally identifiable information you have shared with us is generally one of the business assets that will be transferred.  in such a situation, the personally identifiable information transferred will remain subject to the promises made in this privacy policy or subsequent policies to which you have consented.

somewhere in... is not in a position to guarantee a 100% secure data transmission over the internet or mobile networks.  somewhere in... cannot ensure or warrant the security of any information you transmit to us and you do so at your own risk.  when somewhere in... receives your transmission, somewhere in... makes best effort to ensure security on our systems.

somewhere in... provides its visitors with the opportunity to opt-out of receiving communication from somewhere in… at the point where information about the visitor is requested.  somewhere in… gives you the option to get personal information changed or deleted from our database.  this can be done by sending an email to _privacy@somewherein.net_ or by sending a letter to our street address.  any issue regarding your privacy concern regarding the use of somewhere in...’s services will be taken seriously and you will be contacted upon us receiving your concern.  in a few cases, honoring such requests may make it difficult for us to provide you a good service and may in worst case require us to terminate our relationship with you.

somewhere in… will regularly revise and update its privacy policy, and will publish changes to the policy at our website.  check out our website regularly to keep yourself updated.
